{
    "introduction": "Answer the questions honestly",
    "questions": [
        {"question": "Do you even lift?",
            "answers": {"Olympic": [1, 1, 0, 1, 2, 1], "Power": [1, 2, 0, 1, 3, 2], "Sometimes": [-1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0], "No": [-1, 0, 0, 0, 0, -2]}},
        {"question": "Are you dating anyone?",
            "answers": {"One girl": [1, 2, 0, 2, 1, 1], "Multiple girls": [2, 2, 0, 2, 2, 1], "Nobody": [-1, -1, 0, -2, -2, -1], "I've given up": [-3, -2, 0, -2, -5, -2]}},
        {"question": "Out with a girl - who pays?",
            "answers": {"She does": [-2, 0, 1, -1, 2, 1], "I do": [2, 2, -1, 1, -1, 1], "We split": [-1, -1, 0, 0, 0, 1], "I don't go out with girls": [-2, -1, 1, -1, -1, 0]}},
        {"question": "What's your income (where you live)?",
            "answers": {"Under 25th Percentile": [-2, -3, -4, -2, -3, -3], "25th Percentile": [-1, -1, -2, 0, -1, -1], "50th Percentile": [2, 1, 1, 2, 2, 2], "Over 90th Percentile": [5, 4, 5, 4, 5, 5]}},
        {"question": "How old are you?",
            "answers": {"18-25": [-3, -1, 4, 3, 0, -3], "25-35": [3, 2, 1, 1, 2, 2], "35-45": [3, 3, -3, -1, 1, 3], "Older than 45": [4, 3, -5, -3, -2, 3]}},
        {"question": "Do you have professional goals you're working towards?",
            "answers": {"That's my life mission": [4, 2, 3, -1, 2, 3], "Not as much as I'd like, but yes": [2, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1], "I just want a paycheck": [-1, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0], "I don't care about my career": [-2, -3, -2, 0, -2, 0]}},
        {"question": "How much can you squat?",
            "answers": {"I don't know": [-2, -1, 0, -1, -1, -2], "Less than my body weight": [-1, 0, 0, 0, 0, -1], "1.5x my body weight": [2, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1], "Over 2.x my body weight": [3, 3, -1, 2, 3, 3]}},
        {"question": "When was the last time you kissed a girl?",
            "answers": {"More than 6 months": [-3, -3, 0, -3, -3, -1], "More than 1 month": [-2, -2, 0, -1, -2, 0], "More than 1 week": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "Less than 1 week": [1, 1, 0, 2, 2, 1]}},
        {"question": "Are you in debt (exclude house)?",
            "answers": {"Only a little": [-2, -1, -2, 0, -1, -2], "I've got major debt": [-3, -2, -5, -1, -2, -2], "I've got savings": [3, 3, 3, 0, 2, 2], "I'm pretty much even": [0, 0, -1, 0, 0, 0]}},
        {"question": "I know my way around a club/party/social event?",
            "answers": {"Only a little": [-1, -2, 0, -2, -1, -1], "I'm terrible socially": [-3, -3, 0, -4, -4, -3], "I can hold my own": [1, 2, 0, 2, 1, 0], "I'm the life of the party": [2, 2, 0, 3, 3, 2]}},
        {"question": "Does your job involve violence or force?",
            "answers": {"My job is allowed to use lethal force": [2, 2, -1, 2, 3, 5], "I'm allowed to rough people/things up": [2, 1, 0, 0, 2, 3], "I have a non-violent job": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "I have a nuturing job": [-1, -1, 0, -1, -2, -3]}},
        {"question": "Are you involved in active sports?",
            "answers": {"I am not active": [-2, 0, 0, 0, -2, -1], "Sometimes": [0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0], "I am extremely active": [2, 2, 0, 1, 2, 2], "I am extremely active in a dangerous sport": [3, 3, 0, 2, 3, 3]}},
        {"question": "Do you have strong eye contact?",
            "answers": {"No, I always look down": [-3, -2, 0, -2, -2, -3], "Sometimes": [0, 1, 0, -1, -2, -2], "I am pretty good": [2, 2, 0, 2, 2, 2], "I don't pay attention": [-1, 0, 0, -2, -1, 0]}},
        {"question": "Are you physically flirty?",
            "answers": {"I am always hugging and touching": [1, 1, 0, 1, 2, 1], "I'm very closed off": [-1, 0, 0, -1, -2, -1], "When I get comfortable": [0, 0, 0, 2, 1, 1], "I'm not flirty": [-1, 0, 0, -1, -4, -1]}},
        {"question": "A guy at a party doesn't like your clothing style and laughs at you - what do you do?",
            "answers": {"Get in his face. It's a fight.": [-1, 1, 0, -1, 2, 3], "Make fun of him right back": [1, 2, 0, 2, 1, 1], "Try to figure out what you did wrong": [-2, -2, 0, -2, -2, -3], "Wait, who is he?": [2, 2, 0, 2, 1, 2]}},
        {"question": "If a girl gave you her phone number, you texted her to go out, and she told you she was busy, what should you assume that means?",
            "answers": {"She's really busy": [0, -1, 0, -1, -1, -1], "She's clearly not interested": [1, 1, 0, 1, 2, 0], "She just needs me to show her I'm invested": [-2, -2, 0, -2, -2, -2], "Wait, who is she?": [3, 2, 0, 2, 3, 2]}},
        {"question": "How should you react to her being busy?",
            "answers": {"Send her a bunch of texts": [-3, -3, 0, -3, -3, -3], "Send her another text in a few days": [0, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0], "Oh well, better luck next time": [1, 0, 0, 2, 1, 0], "Wait, who is she?": [3, 2, 0, 2, 3, 2]}},
        {"question": "Your boss asks you to work late. You've never received any promotion or raise - what do you do?",
            "answers": {"I'm already my own boss": [4, 3, 2, 2, 3, 3], "Complain to him": [-3, -3, -1, -2, -2, -3], "Work": [-1, 1, 1, 1, 0, -1], "Refuse tactfully": [1, 2, -1, 1, 1, 1]}},
        {"question": "Taking advantage of others is?",
            "answers": {"Terribly immoral": [-2, -1, -2, 2, -1, -1], "Sadly, sometimes necessary": [2, 2, 2, 1, 2, 2], "Absolutely required": [3, 1, 3, -1, 2, 3], "I don't know how": [-3, -1, -1, -1, -2, -1]}},
        {"question": "Do you ever lie?",
            "answers": {"I will always tell the truth": [1, 0, -1, -1, -1, 0], "I'll stretch the truth": [2, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0], "Without discipline": [-3, -3, -2, -2, -2, -1], "I'm an adept liar": [3, 2, 2, 2, 2, 2]}},
        {"question": "Are you in a long-term relationship?",
            "answers": {"I'm married": [-2, 2, -6, 2, 3, -2], "I've never dated anyone": [-3, -2, 0, -2, -3, -2], "No": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "Yes": [2, 2, 0, 2, 3, 1]}},
        {"question": "Are you able to keep frame?",
            "answers": {"What's frame?": [-2, 0, 0, -1, -2, -3], "I make my own reality": [3, 1, 1, 1, 3, 3], "I have terrible frame": [-3, -2, 0, -1, -3, -3], "So-so": [2, 2, 0, 2, 3, 1]}},
        {"question": "In a group of other men, do you lead?",
            "answers": {"I am always the leader": [3, 3, 1, 1, 2, 2], "I command respect, but don't lead": [1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0], "I am still a follower": [-1, -1, -1, -1, -2, -2], "I have trouble interacting in groups": [-2, -2, -2, -2, -3, -2]}},
        {"question": "Are you stoic?",
            "answers": {"I have almost complete control over my emotions": [2, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1], "I sometimes find my emotions hard to control": [1, 0, 0, -1, 0, 0], "I am somewhat unpredictable when it comes to how I feel": [-2, -1, -1, -2, -1, 0], "I can barely control what I feel": [-3, -2, -1, -2, -2, -1]}},
        {"question": "Have you accepted that you will die?",
            "answers": {"It will happen. I understand that, viscerally, and it does not bother me.": [3, 1, 1, 1, 2, 2], "I know intellectually that it will happen": [1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "I don't even think about it": [-1, 0, 0, 1, 0, -1], "It really bothers me": [-2, -1, -1, -1, -1, -2]}},
        {"question": "Do you know any useful skills?",
            "answers": {"I don't have any skills": [-4, -1, -2, -1, -2, -1], "I have skills but not useful ones": [-1, -1, -1, 0, -1, 0], "I have incredibly useful and in demand skills": [2, 2, 2, 2, 2, 1], "Not only do I have useful skills, I can also easily leverage the talents of others": [4, 3, 3, 2, 2, 2]}},
        {"question": "How tactful are you?",
            "answers": {"I say whatever comes to mind": [-2, -2, -2, -3, -2, -2], "I say whatever I want, when I want": [3, -1, -2, -1, 2, 2], "I know when to control what I say": [2, 1, 2, 2, 1, 0], "I am very adept at conversations, including leading them": [3, 2, 2, 2, 2, 1]}},
        {"question": "Are you masculine?",
            "answers": {"I'm a man's man": [4, 2, 2, 1, 3, 3], "I want and work towards being more masculine": [2, 1, 1, 1, 2, 1], "I try to get in touch with my softer side": [-2, -1, 0, 2, -2, -2], "I think 'masculinity' is very toxic": [-2, 0, -1, 0, -3, -3]}},
        {"question": "About how tall are you?",
            "answers": {"Very short": [-2, -1, -1, 0, -2, -3], "Short": [-1, -1, -1, 0, -1, -2], "Average": [0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0], "Tall": [3, 2, 2, 2, 2, 2]}},
        {"question": "Would you theoretically commit a crime to get ahead?",
            "answers": {"Absolutely not": [-2, 2, -1, 2, -2, -3], "Maybe a small crime": [-1, 1, 0, 1, -1, -2], "I would commit at least a small crime if it would help me": [2, -1, 1, -1, 1, 2], "I would commit any crime necessary": [4, -2, 2, -2, 2, 3]}},
        {"question": "Morality is?",
            "answers": {"Absolute": [1, 0, 0, 0, -1, 1], "Relative": [-1, 1, 0, 1, -2, -2], "I don't believe in morality": [-2, -1, 1, -1, 1, 1], "My morality is whatever benefits me": [0, -1, 2, -1, 2, 3]}}
    ]
}